<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>写作 on i 悦读</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 写作 on i 悦读</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:21 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HBR Guide to Better Business Writing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/hbr-guide-to-better-business-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:21 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/hbr-guide-to-better-business-writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Packed with concise, practical tips from leading experts―and examples that make them easy to apply―the HBR Guides provide smart answers to your most pressing work challenges. Arm yourself with the advice you need to succeed on the job, from the most trusted brand in business. HBR Guide to Better Business Writing, by writing expert Bryan A. Garner: Learn how to write clear, persuasive business documents―from emails to proposals to reports―that get results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simply English: An A-Z of Avoidable Errors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/simply-english-an-a-z-of-avoidable-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:20 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/simply-english-an-a-z-of-avoidable-errors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The author of the best-selling Strictly English wages war on bad English&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In his best-selling Strictly English Simon Heffer explained how to write and speak our language well. In Simply English he offers an entertaining and supremely useful A-Z guide to frequent errors, common misunderstandings and stylistic howlers. What is the difference between amend and emend, between imply and infer, and between uninterested and disinterested? When should one put owing to rather than due to? Why should the temptation to write actually, basically or at this moment in time always be strenuously resisted? How does one use an apostrophe correctly, ensure that one understands what alibi really means, and avoid the perils of the double negative?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>后浪创意写作教室：从入门到写出畅销小说（套装共6册）</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/%E4%BB%8E%E5%85%A5%E9%97%A8%E5%88%B0%E5%86%99%E5%87%BA%E7%95%85%E9%94%80%E5%B0%8F%E8%AF%B4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/%E4%BB%8E%E5%85%A5%E9%97%A8%E5%88%B0%E5%86%99%E5%87%BA%E7%95%85%E9%94%80%E5%B0%8F%E8%AF%B4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介&#34;&gt;内容简介：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《小说的八百万种写法》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本书由劳伦斯•布洛克在《作家文摘》开设十四年的写作专栏结集整理而成，涉及小说创作过程中的方方面面，本书出版四十余年畅销不衰，此版由布洛克亲自更新修订，新、旧观点的碰撞让这本创作秘籍更加富有生机。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《畅销作家写作全技巧》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一本独具特色的小说创作技巧指南，由日本推理小说家大泽在昌所开办的一系列“小说课堂”讲座内容汇集精选而成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《写小说最重要的十件事》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本书是厄休拉•勒古恩主持“写作工作坊”时的课堂讲义，也是她多年创作及阅读经验的浓缩，聚焦于叙事文与虚构写作最重要的十件事：语言的音乐性、文字间的有机作用、结构与调性、叙述者的视角与口吻……&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《小说的骨架：好提纲成就好故事》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本书破除你对提纲可能存在的错误认知，逐点指出写提纲的趣味、好处和技巧，让你的小说框架、层次和节奏都能得到方向性的保障。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《发现你的创造力类型》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本书提出了“创作型人格”这一概念及其5种类型，对每种类型都有详细的特征、类型细分、优势、短板及其改进方法描述，范围涵盖音乐、舞蹈、文学、绘画、影视等文艺领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《作家的灵感宝库》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本书是弗雷德•怀特结合三十多年教学经验编纂的一部“灵感辞典”。冒险、征服、悬疑、爱情、成长、逃离、寻找……无论读者想写什么题材，都可以在这本书中找到灵感。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;作者简介&#34;&gt;作者简介：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《小说的八百万种写法》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;劳伦斯·布洛克，出生于美国布法罗，后定居纽约市。当代欧美“硬汉派”侦探小说标杆，全球知名推理小说家。其曾多次获得爱伦•坡奖、夏姆斯奖、马耳他之鹰奖，并且得到了“美国推理作家协会”颁发的终身大师奖、“英国推理作家协会”颁发的钻石匕首奖等推理小说界重要大奖。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《畅销作家写作全技巧》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大泽在昌，1956年出生于日本爱知县名古屋市，日本著名推理小说作家、畅销书作家。其代表作为《新宿鲛》系列，曾获得日本推理作家协会奖、吉川英治文学新人奖、直木赏、日本冒险小说赏等奖项。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《写小说最重要的十件事》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;厄休拉•勒古恩（1929-2018），生于美国加州伯克利，世界著名奇幻、科幻小说家，被称为“科幻小说女王”。曾获7次雨果奖、6次星云奖、21次轨迹奖，她还曾获美国国家图书奖、卡夫卡奖及美国科幻奇幻作家协会“大师”称号、《洛杉矶时报》“罗伯特•基尔希终身成就奖”等荣誉。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
