<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>口语 on i 悦读</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%8F%A3%E8%AF%AD/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 口语 on i 悦读</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:59:30 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/%E5%8F%A3%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Well-Spoken Thesaurus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/the-well-spoken-thesaurus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:59:30 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/the-well-spoken-thesaurus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, as replacements for absolutely,A&amp;quot; Roget&amp;rsquo;s thesaurus lists several adverbs&amp;ndash;A&amp;quot;extremely,A&amp;quot; exactly,A&amp;quot; perfectlyA&amp;quot;; The Well-Spoken Thesaurus provides both words and phrases&amp;ndash;A&amp;quot;categorically,A&amp;quot; without question,A&amp;quot; by any measureA&amp;quot;&amp;ndash;that offer greater flexibility in shaping a potent, poetic sentence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fine Art of Small Talk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/the-fine-art-of-small-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:19 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/the-fine-art-of-small-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prices for items sold by Amazon AU and third party sellers include NZ GST (if applicable). For items sold by Amazon Global Store, NZ GST will be calculated at checkout. For further information please see Details&#xA;In this bestselling guide to social success, communication expert Debra Fine reveals the techniques and strategies anyone can use to make small talk in any situation.&#xA;Does striking up a conversation with a stranger make your stomach do flip-flops? Do you spend time hiding out in the bathroom at social gatherings? Do you dread the very thought of networking? Is scrolling your phone a crutch to avoid interacting?&#xA;Help is on the way with The Fine Art of Small Talk, the classic guide that&amp;rsquo;s now revised for the modern era. Small talk is more than just chitchat; it&amp;rsquo;s a valuable tool to help you climb the corporate ladder, widen your business and social circles, and boost your self-confidence. With practical advice and simple conversation &amp;lsquo;cheat sheets,&amp;rsquo; this book offers easy-to-learn techniques that will allow you to feel comfortable in any type of social situation-from a video meeting to a first date to a cocktail party where you don&amp;rsquo;t know a soul. Communication expert Debra Fine will show you how to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Talk: Make Effective Feedback Your Superpower</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/lets-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:18 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/lets-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prices for items sold by Amazon AU and third party sellers include NZ GST (if applicable). For items sold by Amazon Global Store, NZ GST will be calculated at checkout. For further information please see Details&#xA;A game-changing model for giving effective feedback to peers, employees, or even your boss&amp;ndash;without offending or demotivating.&#xA;How are you supposed to tell someone that they&amp;rsquo;re not meeting expectations without crushing their spirit? Regular feedback, when delivered skillfully, can turn average performers into the hardest workers and stars into superstars. Yet many see it as an awkward chore: Recent studies have revealed 37% of managers dread giving feedback, and 65% of employees wish their managers gave more feedback.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
