<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>浪漫 on i 悦读</title>
    <link>https://iyuedu.top/tags/%E6%B5%AA%E6%BC%AB/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 浪漫 on i 悦读</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 06:01:05 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://iyuedu.top/tags/%E6%B5%AA%E6%BC%AB/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Just for the Summer</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/just-for-the-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 06:01:05 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/just-for-the-summer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一部犀利而又精彩的夏季小说，作者是《纽约时报》畅销书《Yours Truly》的作者， 它将使读者开怀大笑，流下幸福的眼泪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;贾斯汀身上有一道诅咒，多亏 Reddit 上的一个帖子，这道诅咒现在传遍了整个互联网。他约会的每个女人在分手后都会找到自己的灵魂伴侣。当一个女人带着同样的问题偷偷溜进他的私信时，他们想出了一个计划：他们会约会然后分手。他们的诅咒会互相抵消，他们都会找到他们一生的挚爱。这是一个疯狂的想法……而且它可能真的有效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;艾玛原本没有计划她的下一个巡回护士任务是在明尼苏达州，但她和她最好的朋友一致认为和贾斯汀约会是一个不容错过的好机会，尤其是当他们可以在明尼通卡湖的一个私人岛屿上租一间可爱的小屋时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这本应是一场短暂的恋情，只为一个夏天。但当艾玛有毒的母亲出现，贾斯汀不得不承担起他三个兄弟姐妹的监护权时，他们突然之间要处理比他们预想的更多的事情——包括对彼此产生真正的感情。如果这次命运真的把完美的一对带到了一起呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;作者简介-------&#34;&gt;作者简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Abby Jimenez&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Material</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/good-material/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 06:01:03 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/good-material/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every relationship has one beginning.&#xA;This one has two endings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Andy loves Jen. Jen loved Andy.&#xA;And he can&amp;rsquo;t work out why she stopped.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under One Roof</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/under-one-roof/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/under-one-roof/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A scientist should never cohabitate with her annoyingly hot nemesis – it leads to combustion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Girl Complex</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/good-girl-complex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 06:59:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/good-girl-complex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mackenzie &amp;ldquo;Mac&amp;rdquo; Cabot is a people pleaser. Her demanding parents. Her prep school friends. Her long-time boyfriend. It&amp;rsquo;s exhausting, really, always following the rules. Unlike most twenty-year-olds, all she really wants to do is focus on growing her internet business, but first she must get a college degree at her parents&amp;rsquo; insistence. That means moving to the beachside town of Avalon Bay, a community made up of locals and the wealthy students of Garnet College.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Rainbows End</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/where-rainbows-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 06:59:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/where-rainbows-end/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;True love, friendship and luck - a warm-hearted novel about where fate can lead you From naughty children to rebellious teenagers, Rosie and Alex have stuck by each other through thick and thin. But just as they&amp;rsquo;re discovering the joys of teenage nights on the town and dating disasters, they&amp;rsquo;re separated. Alex&amp;rsquo;s family moves from Dublin to America - and Alex goes with them. For good. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s lost without her best friend. But on the eve of her departure to join Alex in Boston, Rosie gets news that will change her life forever - and keep her at home in Ireland. Their magical connection sees them through the ups and downs of each other&amp;rsquo;s lives but neither of them knows whether their friendship can really survive the years and miles - as well as new relationships. And at the back of Rosie&amp;rsquo;s mind is whether they were meant to be more than just good friends all along. Misunderstandings, circumstances and sheer bad luck have kept them out of each others&amp;rsquo; arms, but when presented with the ultimate opportunity, will they gamble everything - including their friendship - for true love? Destiny, Alex and Rosie discover, is a funny thing and fate isn&amp;rsquo;t quite done with them yet&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hating Game</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-hating-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 06:59:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-hating-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lucy Hutton and Joshua Templeman hate each other. Not dislike. Not begrudgingly tolerate. Hate. And they have no problem displaying their feelings through a series of ritualistic passive aggressive maneuvers as they sit across from each other, executive assistants to co-CEOs of a publishing company. Lucy can’t understand Joshua’s joyless, uptight, meticulous approach to his job. Joshua is clearly baffled by Lucy’s overly bright clothes, quirkiness, and Pollyanna attitude.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Roughest Draft</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-roughest-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:59:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-roughest-draft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They were cowriting literary darlings until they hit a plot hole that turned their lives upside down.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Catch by Amy Lea</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-catch-by-amy-lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:59:26 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/the-catch-by-amy-lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介-------&#34;&gt;内容简介  · · · · · ·&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;捕获（暂译）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一段欢喜冤家的浪漫喜剧之旅。网红梅兰妮为挽救濒临破产的时尚品牌，毅然前往加拿大农村。在那里，她邂逅了渔夫埃文，但他却与印象中加拿大人的传统友善截然不同。然而，一次意外的划船事故让埃文住进了医院，他的家人竟误将梅兰妮当作他的未婚妻。于是，他们决定共同演绎一场为期一周的假订婚。他们能否成功维持这场虚假的订婚，而不让感情趁机滋长？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A grumpy lobster fisherman tosses a fashion influencer’s impeccably curated life overboard in the next romantic comedy from international bestselling author Amy Lea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>凯特·莫顿悬疑浪漫经典</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/%E5%87%AF%E7%89%B9%E8%8E%AB%E9%A1%BF%E6%82%AC%E7%96%91%E6%B5%AA%E6%BC%AB%E7%BB%8F%E5%85%B8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/books/%E5%87%AF%E7%89%B9%E8%8E%AB%E9%A1%BF%E6%82%AC%E7%96%91%E6%B5%AA%E6%BC%AB%E7%BB%8F%E5%85%B8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;内容简介&#34;&gt;内容简介：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《钟表匠的女儿》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我对接下来的计划只字未提，甚至连一句正式的告别都没说……&#xA;我以为，我们还有时间，还会再见面。&#xA;如今，我已在伯奇伍德庄园里生活了155年。&#xA;幼时，他们说我是钟表匠的女儿，是另有用途的小女孩；&#xA;成年前，爱德华说我是他的缪斯，是他无法逃离的命运；&#xA;那年夏天之后，世人说我是小偷，是冒名顶替的女骗子。&#xA;而我的真实姓名，早已随着那年夏天的真相，深埋在时间的细流之下，一去不复返。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《湖边小屋的谎言》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1933年仲夏，湖边小屋中的埃德温家族迎来了一年一度的盛大派对，草地上宾客云集。半夜12点，一枚烟花腾空而起，照亮黑夜。16岁的爱丽丝看见，森林里一个熟悉的身影一闪而过。第二天，她蹒跚学步的弟弟从世界上永远消失了。爱丽丝没有告诉任何人，自己可能是失踪案的罪魁祸首。余生，陪伴她的将只有懊悔和愧疚。&#xA;2003年夏天，一个停职的女警探意外闯进废弃的湖边小屋。很快她会看到，攀爬疯长的藤曼和破败不堪的木门背后，70年前那场谎言酿成的悲剧，即将苏醒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《雾中回忆》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1924年，里弗顿庄园正在举办一场盛大的社交晚宴。觥筹交错之际，诗人罗比徘徊在黑黢黢的湖边。突然，一声枪响。人们都以为诗人的自杀是一个感伤浪漫的故事，但真相只有女仆格蕾丝知道。&#xA;1999年，一位电影制片人正在拍摄一部关于诗人罗比的电影，她邀请现年98岁的考古学家格蕾丝重返里弗顿庄园评估细节。年迈的格蕾丝再也抵挡不住记忆的洪流和秘密的啮噬。过去，开始复活了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《她一生的秘密》&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她以为她会在秘密中巧妙地度过这一生，但她错了，秘密永远会寻找出口。&#xA;16岁的洛瑞尔正躲在树屋里畅想未来，但这天下午将成为她未来人生中永远挥之不去的阴影——她将目睹一场血案，而这和她母亲有关。&#xA;五十年来，秘密依然是秘密，但一张照片的突然出现让洛瑞尔必须拼凑出母亲命运转折的真相。随着洛瑞尔一步步深入母亲内心的纠葛，大半个世纪之前的友谊、爱情、逃亡和冒险都开始一一复活。&#xA;翻开这本书，抵达时光深处，去读懂一颗孤独守密者的心。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
