<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Feature on i 悦读</title>
    <link>https://iyuedu.top/tags/feature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Feature on i 悦读</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:51:48 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://iyuedu.top/tags/feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>药检阳性归咎于食品污染即可免责？反兴奋剂机构展开调查</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-08-01/2024-08-01-antidoping-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:51:48 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-08-01/2024-08-01-antidoping-agency/</guid>
      <description>Antidoping Agency Acknowledges Concern Over Use of Tainted Food as Excuse MICHAEL S. SCHMIDT, JENNY VRENTAS, TARIQ PANJA&#xA;The global antidoping regulator disclosed on Tuesday that it is investigating why athletes in China and other countries who are testing positive for banned drugs are escaping discipline through claims that they have unwittingly ingested the performance-enhancing substances through food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>中国人工智能进步加速，正缩小与美国差距</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-29/2024-07-23-the-ai-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:11:37 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-29/2024-07-23-the-ai-gap/</guid>
      <description>China Is Closing the A.I. Gap With the United States MEAGHAN TOBIN, CADE METZ&#xA;At the World Artificial Intelligence Conference in Shanghai this month, start-up founder Qu Dongqi showed off a video he had recently posted online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>拜登宣布退选：放弃寻求连任，转而支持哈里斯</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-23/2024-07-23-bidens-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 09:11:37 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-23/2024-07-23-bidens-decision/</guid>
      <description>Biden’s decision upends the race less than four months before Election Day. Here’s the latest. MICHAEL D. SHEAR&#xA;President Biden, 81, abandoned his bid for re-election on Sunday as he caved to relentless pressure from his closest allies to drop out of the race amid deep concerns that he was too old and frail to defeat former President Donald J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“美国受到了攻击”：还原特朗普集会遇袭现场</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-15/2024-07-15-americas-under-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:11:37 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-15/2024-07-15-americas-under-attack/</guid>
      <description>‘America’s Under Attack’: A Gleeful Trump Rally Shattered by Gunfire CAMPBELL ROBERTSON&#xA;It was a sweltering Pennsylvania afternoon, hot enough to keep the medics busy as people wilted in the blazing sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>不忍了：新西兰华人准备上街</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-09/2024-07-09-self-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:11:37 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-09/2024-07-09-self-defence/</guid>
      <description>不忍了：新西兰华人要上街了——今天，网络上流传一则“邀请”通知： “为了安全而自卫，绝不投降。”这份通告上写。&#xA;“你是否感到不安全？……如果是的，请来一起参加，向犯罪说不！”&#xA;这是怎么回事？&#xA;难道是因为最近华人少年乘坐公共汽车遭遇种族袭击一事闹得沸沸扬扬，华人这是要上街吗？&#xA;Crime Prevention Group执行委员David Yang告诉发现君，最近这个热点事件的确是一个导火索。&#xA;他说，6月底一名华人少年在乘坐公共交通时，被“某种族的歹徒”无端打伤。&#xA;更令人难以接受的是，奥克兰交通局至今没有为此事道歉。他说。&#xA;“虽然这是一次偶发事件，但也在必然之中。”&#xA;David Yang说，如果奥克兰交通局不需要为公共交通的安全负责，工会方面也表示司机的工作就是开车，不需要维护治安，会不会以后华人女性不敢坐车？这些传递出的信息就是“安全只能自己负责”。&#xA;他说，有鉴于此，奥克兰民安会通过Crime Prevention Group发起了本周六的活动。&#xA;这场活动中，将会在奥克兰市中心Britomart广场，在大庭广众之下“宣讲如何自卫”。&#xA;他说，他们甚至会请武术专家来讲解自卫要领。&#xA;而这场活动的核心，其实是向新西兰联合政府表明华人的态度。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>法国大选：左翼联盟崛起，联合阻击极右翼</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-09/2024-07-09-french-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:11:36 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-09/2024-07-09-french-election/</guid>
      <description>法国大选：左翼联盟崛起，联合阻击极右翼 French Election Yields Deadlock as Left Surges and Far Right Comes Up Short ROGER COHEN&#xA;France faced a hung parliament and deep political uncertainty after the three main political groups of the left, center and right emerged from snap legislative elections on Sunday with large shares of the vote but nothing approaching an absolute majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>工党时隔14年赢得大选，英国“转向”前途仍不乐观</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-07/as-britain-votes-change-is-in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 20:11:36 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-07/as-britain-votes-change-is-in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>工党时隔14年赢得大选，英国“转向”前途仍不乐观 As Britain Votes, Change Is in the Air. Optimism, Not So Much. 最新消息：工党赢得英国大选，基尔·斯塔默将成为英国下一任首相。&#xA;Voters went to the polls in Britain on Thursday in a dyspeptic mood, many of them frustrated with the Conservative government and skeptical that any replacement can unravel the tangle of problems hobbling the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>新任英国首相的第一天</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-04/nukes-and-king-charles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 11:15:17 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/2024-07-04/nukes-and-king-charles/</guid>
      <description>Nukes and King Charles—but no door key The first 24 hours for a new British prime minister are odd, and busy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>研究表明，这些超加工食品可能会缩短你的寿命</title>
      <link>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/these-ultraprocessed-foods-may-shorten-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:11:36 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://iyuedu.top/posts/news/these-ultraprocessed-foods-may-shorten-your-life/</guid>
      <description>These ultraprocessed foods may shorten your life, study says 一项新研究表明，食用过多超加工食品可能会缩短寿命。&#xA;Eating higher levels of ultraprocessed food may shorten lifespans by more than 10%, according to a new, unpublished study of over 500,000 people whom researchers followed for nearly three decades.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
